Welcome to the Department
of Dairy Science!
Hokkaido O
Hokkaido Ooezo Agricultu
Hokkaido Ooezo Agricultural High School
酪農科学科の諸君 入学おめでとう
For the next year,
you will live in student housing
これから１年間 君たちは全員 寮生活をしながら
pursuing your studies, as well
as practicums in agriculture.
勉学に励み 農場実習をすることになる
We have many livestock, so there's
no such thing as a holiday on the farm!
様々な家畜を扱っているので
基本 農場が休みということはない
Here's the cattle shed!
ここが牛舎
In Japan, dairy cows are
generally kept in enclosures,
日本では まだつなぎ飼いの酪農が一般的だが
but here at Ezonoo,
ここ エゾノーでは より自然に近い形で 牛を飼う…
we have implemented a
pasture-based dairy system
Ugh!
くさーっ 何でみんな平気なんだ
that allows us to keep our cows...
How can you all stand the smell?
It's huge!
でかっ
Oh, sorry.
あー 悪い 悪い
I was just changing this
one's straw bedding.
今 こっこの寝わら替えてたんだわ
Minami-sensei, can you put
him back in his stall?
南先生 そいつ寝床に入れといて
Sure thing.
はいよ
You're just leaving him there?
ほっとくの 逃げないのかな
Aww, so cute.
Won't he run off?
Maybe I should grab a hold of him...
捕まえといた方がいいんじゃ…
Hey!
こらー
Oh, where'd he run off to?
あれ あいつどこ行った
A student chased him
toward the fields.
仔追い掛けて 農地の方へ
What an idiot.
バカでねえの
He would've come along
if you held a feeding pail.
哺乳バケツ持ってれば 勝手についてくるべさ
Well, he's gone off somewhere.
どっか行っちゃいましたね
Uh-oh, we have a lost one.
あーあ 迷子だ
Blue skies...
青い空
The great outdoors...
うなる自然
No cell reception...
通じない携帯
A clingy calf...
なれなれしい子牛
Where am I?
ここ どこ
Episode 1
Welcome to
Ezonoo
この…
Why, you—
It's your fault.
お前のせいだ
All your fault, you jerk!
お前のせいだ この野郎
熊出たら いけにえにして 逃げてやるからな
If a bear shows up,
I'll sacrifice you and run!
Hey, did you hear that?
おい 何か 音しなかったか
A... bear?
あっ 熊
Found you!
見つけた
Uh, a Horseman of the Apocalypse?!
せ…世紀末覇者
Uh, Hachiken-kun, right?
えーと 八軒君だっけ 迎えに来たよ
I've come to get you.
You okay?
大丈夫
A feeding pail?
哺乳バケツ そんな簡単な方法が…
It's that simple?
Animals just run faster
when you chase them.
動物って 追い掛けると 余計逃げるよ
So that's it...
そういうもんか
But why the horse?
でも 何で馬
馬術部から借りてきたの
I got one from the equestrian club.
I can go anywhere on a horse.
これなら どこでも行けるから
Wow, I'm impressed that you can
control such a huge horse.
すげえな こんなでかい馬 乗りこなしてるなんて
It's just a plow horse.
農耕馬だよ
I've been riding since I was little,
so I'm used to it.
小さいころから乗ってるから 慣れてるだけ
My family has a farm
with cows and horses.
うちは 牛と馬飼ってる農家でさ
I thought I might carry
on the family business,
後を継ごうかなーと思って この学校に来たんだ
so I came to this school.
What was your name again?
名前 何さんだっけ
I'm your classmate, Mikage.
同じクラスの御影だよ
Mikage Aki. Nice to meet you.
御影アキ よろしくね
Dairy Science
Welcome, students!
入学おめでとう
I'm your homeroom teacher, Sakuragi.
担任の桜木だ ３年間よろしくな
We'll be together for
the next three years.
You've been living in the dorms,
もう 寮生活に入ってるから お互い顔合わせしてると思うけど
so you probably know each other already.
But let's have everyone
introduce themselves.
あらためて 自己紹介してもらおうかな
I'm Aikawa Shinnosuke,
from Makubetsu East Junior High.
幕別東中から来ました 相川進之介です
I want to become a vet.
獣医 目指してます
Komaba Ichirou, from Shimizu
First Junior High!
清水第一中 出身 駒場 一郎
I'm gonna carry on the family
dairy business once I graduate!
卒業後は 実家の酪農 継ぐつもりです
I'm in the baseball club!
部活は野球部 甲子園 目指します
We're gonna try for the nationals!
I am Inada Tamako, from Obihiro
Kawanishi Central Junior High.
帯広川西中央中から来ました 稲田 多摩子
I'd like to study agribusiness management
農業経営を学んで 世界に出ても負けない農業を目指します
and set up a world-class farm.
I'm Tokiwa Keiji!
常盤 恵次
From Nakasatsunai South Junior High!
中札内南中 出身
I'm gonna take up my
family's poultry farm!
実家継いで 鶏農家やるっす
Yoshino Mayumi,
from Shimourahoro Junior High.
下浦幌中 吉野まゆみ
I want to start up a
cheese business using
将来は実家の牛乳を使って チーズ工房を立ち上げたいです
milk from my family's dairy farm.
What's with these guys?
何なの こいつら
Next, Hachiken.
次 八軒 八軒
Hachiken!
Oh, okay!
あっ はい
Hey, it's that guy who got lost
during the campus orientation tour.
あっ この前の場内見学会で迷子になってたやつだ
Oh, you're right.
ホントだ
I'm Hachiken Yuugo,
from Shin Sapporo Junior High.
新札幌中から来ました
八軒 勇吾です
Um, nice to meet you all.
えーと よろしくお願いします
Shin Sapporo Junior High?
新札幌中？
Isn't that a prep school?
すげえ進学校じゃね
About Practicums
Forming Teams
We're now going to split the forty
of you up into eight teams.
これから このクラス４０名を８班に分ける
Each team will work
together on chores like
朝夕の家畜舎実習などを この班でやってもらうことになる
the AM-PM barn practicum.
Girls
Boys
You'll draw straws to
form five-person teams.
くじ引きで ５人一組を つくるからな
Be nice to your teammates
for the next three years.
３年間 仲良くしろよ
Ooezo Agricultural High School Dormitory
for Future Agriculture Managers
Here, eat this.
これ 食ってけよ
You've still got a ways
to go until breakfast.
朝飯まで 時間あるから
Thanks.
あんがと
G'luck. Night!
頑張れよ おやすみ
I'm sleepy...
眠い 寒い
Cold...
Man...
たまんないね
The livestock practicum lasts
for a whole week, right?
家畜実習って １週間 続くんだよね
Yeah...
Uh, you're...
えっと
Aikawa. Aikawa Shinnosuke.
相川 相川 進之介
Nice to meet you, Hachiken-kun.
よろしく 八軒君
Same here.
よろしく
You want to be a vet, right?
獣医 目指してるんだっけ
Yeah.
It's my childhood dream.
小さいころからの夢 もう くじけそうだけど
I'm already about
to give up, though.
What about you?
八軒君は
If you came from Sapporo
to a high school way out in the boonies,
札幌からわざわざこんな田舎の高校に来たってことは目的あるんでしょ
you must have a reason.
Because it's a boarding school...
寮があるから 帰らなくて済むから
I don't have to go to home.
Get help!
人 集めてこいよ
What about nets?
網は
Nah! Just get help!
いい 人を頼む
Oh, is something going on?
何かあったんすか
Oh, first-years?
おう １年か 男子 手伝ってくれ
Guys, help us out!
The chickens intended for
a practicum got loose!
実習用の鶏が逃げちゃってよ
Oh, uh... Okay, I'll help!
あっ はい やります
But what about our practicum?
でも 実習が…
All right, let's catch 'em quick!
よし ちゃっちゃと捕まえるべ
Wha?!
I'll let the instructor know.
先生には伝えておくわ
Don't hold them back.
足手まといに ならないようにしなさいよ
Hey, Tamako!
おい 多摩子 てめえ
You—
Whew, thank god!
いやー 助かった ありがとな １年坊
Thanks, first-years!
Sure...
いえ…
We should thank you.
お礼しなきゃな
スモークチキン できたら食わせてやるよ
We'll give you some
smoked chicken when it's done!
Yeah!
Which dorm room are you in?
寮生 何号室 名前は
What're your names?
Chicken Coop
Good morning!
おはようございます
Hey! Great work, right off the bat!
おう
初っぱなから いい仕事したじゃねえか
All right, come right in.
じゃ 早速 中に入ってくれ
It's gonna be like this
for three years?
こんなのが ３年間…
Ugh, it stinks...
臭っ
って すげえ
Wow!
It's like an egg factory!
まるで 卵工場だ
Hachiken, Tokiwa, collect the eggs.
八軒と常盤は 卵を集めてくれ
Okay!
へーい
You're good at this.
手際いいな
My family runs a poultry farm.
うち 鶏農家だもーん
But I didn't know the chicken
coop was so systematic.
しかし 鶏舎って すごいシステマチックなんだな
It's only for chickens to
eat feed and lay eggs.
餌 食わされて 卵 産まされるだけのスペースって
But these kinds of efficiency-first
coops that aren't kind to the chickens
でも こういう 効率優先で 鶏に優しくない鶏舎は
are criticized in the West.
欧米とかだと非難されんだぜ
For me, when it's this efficient,
it's just impressive.
ここまで効率的だと 逆に 感心するけど
U-Um...
あ…あのさ
Yeah?
鶏の卵って どっから生まれるの
Where do chicken eggs come from?
Where?
どこって 肛門だろ
The anus, of course.
The same as poop?!
うんこと一緒
Intestines
Ovary
Oviduct
To be more precise,
it's called the cloaca,
正しくは総排泄腔といって 卵管の出口と直接腸がつなが…
and the oviduct opens
directly into the intestine—
A-Aren't these dirty, then?
汚くないのか これ
Well, that's why we're giving
them a good scrub by hand.
だからこうして 全部丁寧に洗って磨いてんだろ
Each egg's full of the farmer's
tender, loving care! Delicious!
卵一個一個に 生産者の気持ちがこもって うんまいぞ
But...
でも でも
But it's like poop!
うんこと一緒じゃねー
Poop...
Ooezo Agricultural High School Dormitory
for Future Agriculture Managers
It's time for breakfast.
朝食の時間です
All students, please report to the dining hall.
寮生は全員 食堂に集まってください
繰り返します 朝食の時間です
I repeat, it's time for breakfast.
寮生は全員 食堂に集まってください
All students, please report to the dining hall.
Wonder what's on the menu.
メニュー な～にかな
It's a silver spoon.
銀の匙だね
Is there a meaning behind it?
何か意味があるのかな
In Europe, they give a newborn
child a silver spoon.
ヨーロッパじゃ
生まれてくる子に 銀のスプーンを贈るんだって
It's to ensure that
they never go hungry.
その子が一生 食べるのに困らないようにって
All right, let's eat...
さあ 飯 飯
Let's eat!
いただきまーす
What's wrong? It'll get cold.
どうした 冷めるぞ
I'll let you have this...
これ やるよ
...to thank you.
さっきのお返し
Really?
ホント やったー
Yay!
The anus...
肛門
Looks delicious!
おいしそー
Wait a minute...
ちょっと待て…
Wait a minute!
ちょっと待て！
うおおお ちょっと待て
Wait a minute!
That came from the anus...
それは 肛門から…
The anus!
肛門からー！！
It's tasty because it's fresh!
やっぱり 新鮮だから おいしいわね
Forget Tamako!
多摩子は どうでもいい
What's the matter?
どうした
This school's hard
on your nerves...
この学校 精神攻撃が多過ぎて
Is it?
そうか この後 数学あんだろ
But math's coming up.
General subjects are harder on my nerves.
俺は 一般教科の方がつらいけどな
Revised Edition
Mathematics I
Finally, time for normal
high school stuff!
やっと まともな高校生活の時間がきたか
Revised Edition
Mathematics I
って さすがは農業高校 薄過ぎだろ
But wow, I'm at an agricultural
high school, all right.
It's way too thin!
The content's sparse, too.
中身も すかすかだし これなら楽勝
I'm gonna ace this for sure!
The true enemy is...
真の敵は…
I'm Yachiyo, in charge
of livestock science.
畜産担当の八千代です
I'll start with the basics.
まず 家畜の基本を教えていきます
Livestock Science
But, because this area has
a lot of dairy farms,
とはいっても この地区は酪農家が多い
the class will emphasize dairy cows.
やはり 乳牛寄りの授業になるけど よろしくな
Okay.
I took advantage of spring break
and already studied the textbook.
春休みを利用して
畜産の教科書を読み込んだ俺に 死角なし
Nothing will stop me!
数値もろもろ 頭にたたき込み済みだ
I've already memorized all the numbers!
I'm gonna get the top
score on the next exam—
次のテストは
Okay, about all the reference
stats in this textbook.
ぶっちぎりで 学年１番を…
えー この教科書にある諸々の資料数値ですが
They're based on the national average.
全国平均から 割り出したものです
The cows in Hokkaido are big,
so those numbers don't fit.
北海道の牛はでかいので 当てになりません
Livestock Science
So we'll use another
reference text in class.
なので
授業では 別資料を使います
Dammit...
チクショー
Campus Motto
Defy Logic  Cooperation  Diligence
Hachiken!
八軒
You're smart, right?
お前 頭 いんだべ
Huh? Not really—
えっ 別に
Teach me math!
数学 教えてくれ
I'm already lost at page one!
もう１ページ目から 訳分からん
But this is junior high stuff.
こんなん 中学レベルじゃん
No, I totally sucked back then, too!
いやぁ 俺 中学でも ダメダメだったの
Besides, I got in here because I was
recommended for being a farmer's son.
だいたい 農家の長男ってだけで
推薦入学だもん
Really?
マジで
Despite scoring one out of five in math,
I got in without taking the entrance exam.
万年数学１でも 入試なしで入れちゃったし
We got in through referral, too,
俺らも推薦だけど そんなにひどくねーぞ
but we weren't that bad!
Don't make us sound bad.
一緒にすんな
My best grade was a three!
俺 最高 ３
What, on a ten-point scale?
１０段階評価？
No, five!
５段階
Me, too! I always got twos in English.
俺も俺も 英語はいつも２
Oh, same here.
あっ 一緒
Man, they're so dumb.
フッ レベル低っ
Yeah?
んだよー
All right...
じゃあ 基本からやる
Want to start with the basics?
Don't underestimate how
dumb I am, though!
けど 俺の頭の悪さ なめんなよ
No problem.
いいよ できるまで付き合うよ
I'll stick with you till you get it.
Really? Thanks!
マジ 感謝
If this is what my
classmates are like,
周りがこんなんなら 学年１番は余裕だな こりゃ
I guess I'll be the top student
in my class, no problem.
First, take X...
まずは このｘを…
What's "X"?
ｘって何
Huh?
Aikawa, you want to be a vet?
相川 お前 獣医志望だって
Yeah.
そうだよ
What's the deal with somatic cell
cloning research these days?
体細胞クローンの研究って 今はどうなってんの
Once TPP kicks into gear,
ＴＰＰの波がきちゃったら
Japan won't be able to compete with
imported agricultural products
高品質の農産物を低コストで大量に作らなきゃ
unless it can grow high-quality produce
in large quantities at low cost.
海外農産物と戦えなくなるべ
Japan won't be able to insist on
not cloning beef cattle anymore.
もう肉牛クローンは駄目とか 言ってらんなくなるっしょ
Hey, I'm interested in that topic.
あら そういう話なら 私も興味あるわ
うーん ちょっと前の研究だと
Well, if we're talking
recent research...
Cloning cows from somatic cells
is a really complicated process,
体細胞クローン牛の作製過程って 複雑だから
so the success rate is really low.
いまだに成功率が低くて
More and more research
institutes are giving up.
研究をやめちゃってる機関が 増えてるんだ
They say clones have
a shorter lifespan,
The genetic blueprint gets reset during the
early developmental stages following insemination,
本来 受精初期発生で分化したゲノム情報が…
but a study found that Dolly
was actually an exception.
実は例外だったっていう 研究が出てて
and as cells proliferate and
differentiation continues...
You need to select good genetic
markers, then do a blastocyst biopsy to...
良質なマーカー遺伝子を…
By silencing the XIST gene on the
X-chromosome, they've improved...
Ｘ染色体のイグジストを…
As for what will happen to the epigenetics of the
recipient's cloned embryos...
Are they speaking in code?!
呪文
Isn't that college-level science?
あれ 大学レベルだよね
Oh, our knowledge is really skewed,
so it's nothing to be proud of.
いやぁ 僕らの知識って すごい偏ってるから
威張れたもんじゃないよ
All right, line up, first-years!
よーし １年生 並べ
本日の体力測定は マラソンです
We'll test your endurance
with a marathon today.
What?!
コースは学校の敷地１周です
One lap around the school campus!
Let's start with warm-ups!
まずは 準備運動
One lap?
１周 意外と楽ちんだね
That's not so bad.
Oh, and by the way...
え～ ちなみに
Our campus, which includes fields
and forest used in practicums,
わが校の実習農地 実習農林を含めた敷地面積は
is the largest in the
nation for a high school.
高校では 全国一でありまして…
One lap covers twenty kilometers.
１周 ２０ｋｍあります
I... want to quit this school already.
もう この学校 辞めたい
Hey! No slacking!
こらー ちんたら走るな
ほら 夕方の家畜当番実習 始まっちまうぞ
Hey, the evening livestock
practicum's about to start.
Gimme a break.
勘弁しろよー
If we don't get this done quickly,
I'll miss club practice.
早く終わらせねえと 部活終わっちまうからよ
You're still up for that?
まだ やる気かよ
Komaba-kun, you already joined a club?
駒場君 もう部活やってんだ
I've been training with
them since spring break.
春休み中から練習に参加してる
Want to join me in the baseball club?
お前らも 野球部どうよ
I don't like sports...
俺 スポーツ嫌い
Neither do I.
僕も苦手だなー
Actually,
つーか 何で この学校は
why the hell does this school have
two baseball fields, anyway?
野球グラウンドが ２面もあるんだよ
This school isn't short on
space, that's for sure.
土地だけは無駄にあるからな この学校
Hey!
お～い
You've joined a club, too, Aki?
アキも もう 部活やってんのかよ
"Aki"?
「アキ」？
うん 春休みから
Yeah, from spring break.
You two seem like good friends.
２人 仲いいんだね
We went to the same junior high.
同じ中学 家も隣だし
We're next-door neighbors, too.
Don't bring a horse all the way here.
お前 こんな所に馬連れてくんなよ
I borrowed him from the neighboring
university, so I'm just moving him.
隣の大学から借りてきて 移動中なの
These two are close, huh...
この２人 仲いいのか
Hachiken-kun, did you
choose a club already?
八軒君はもう部活決めたの
Huh?
えっ いや 俺は特に…
No, I might not join any...
いいかな
It's a requirement to
join one, you know?
この学校 部活は必須だよ
What? Seriously?
嘘 マジ
There are no cultural
clubs, either!
ちなみに文化部はない 全部運動部
It's all athletics!
Damn jock school!
筋肉学校め
If you haven't decided,
決まってないなら 馬術部に入らない
how about the equestrian club?
Horses are so cute!
馬 カワイイよ
Cute?
カワイイ？
So, come check us out sometime!
ねっ 今度見学においでよ
Okay, I will at some point.
うん そのうち…
All right, off we go to the practicum.
ほら 実習行くぞ
Hey, be careful!
おーい 気を付けろよ 大事な商品だぞ
They're a valuable product!
Hachiken, you're exhausted.
八軒 疲れてんなー
And you're fine, Tokiwa?
常盤は平気なのか
Sure, I'm tired,
そりゃ疲れるけど 教科書より実習の方が断然いいね
but I totally prefer practicums
over studying textbooks!
Komaba, you don't look tired at all.
駒場は全然だよな
I get lots of sleep during class!
俺は授業中 たっぷり寝てるからな
Don't be proud of that!
威張んな！！
Feed Store Room
(Biological Production Association: Practicum Room)
White
This... is the last of 'em.
これで最後だ
All right, all done!
よーし 作業 終わり
You can go home!
帰っていいぞー
Thanks.
う～っす
I'm starving!
腹 減ったー
Dinner will be awesome.
ご飯 おいしいだろうなぁ
The wind's really blowing!
風 強っ
Hey!
おーい ニワトリ先生
Chicken-sensei!
Can I borrow some of your students?
生徒 借りてっていいかな
What's the matter?
どうしました
The greenhouse got damaged
by the sudden gust.
突風で 園芸の温室壊れちゃってさ
There's supposed to be
a cold front tonight.
今晩寒波来るっていうし このままじゃ 全部枯れちゃうよ
We could lose our crops to frost!
We can't allow that!
そりゃヤバい 全員出動
All hands on deck!
Hey!
こら～！
Get a firm grip on it, Aikawa!
ちゃんと押さえんか 相川
うっ はい
Okay!
Hey, pull harder!
そっち もっと引っ張れ
Tamako, don't tell me you're
getting blown away by the wind!
多摩子 お前その体重で 飛ばされてんじゃねえ
Hachiken, go help her!
八軒 助けてこい
Why me?
何で 俺が
Damn it...
この…
Crap!
チクショー！！
I... I'm starving.
は…腹 減った…
It's seven.
うわっ ７時かよ
We totally won't make it to
the dining hall in time.
寮の食堂 完璧間に合わねえべ
Nice work!
お疲れ
You've been a huge help.
ホント助かったよ
You guys must be starving!
腹減ったろ 飯食ってけ
Eat up!
Although, it's whatever
we managed to find.
つっても
寄せ集めたもんしかないけどよ
The pickles are from the
gardening instructor.
たくあんは 園芸の先生から
The eggs are from me!
卵は うちからの差し入れだ
Let's eat!
いただきまーす
Gimme the soy sauce!
しょうゆ 早くよこせ
Wait, wait.
待て 待て
こう 黄身をつぶしたところに ざざっと…
Break the yolk, then pour it over!
C'mon, gimme!
ほら よこせ
Not yet. It tastes even
better when you pour it on.
まだまだ
もっと掛けると うまいんだ
You already did.
さっき 掛けたろ
Just three more drops...
いやいやいや あと３滴
It's all black now.
真っ黒じゃねえか
Nah, it needs even more.
いやいや もっと もっと もっと
Super tasty!
超うめえぇぇぇ！！
Damn you, anus...
肛門のくせに…肛門のくせに…
Damn you!
Shut up!
うるせえ 総排泄腔だっつ～の
I told you it's the cloaca.
常盤 肛門からこんなうめえもんが…
Tokiwa, how can something
so tasty come out of an anus?
Chickens are amazing.
鶏って すげえぇぇ
I'm glad you think that...
but kind of mad, too!
うれしいけど 何か腹立つな
Amazing!
すげ～よ～！
Ooezo Agricultural High School Dormitory for Future Agriculture Managers
Nishikawa Hajime
Hachiken Yuugo
Beppu Tarou
I'm beat.
疲れた
I'm tired inside and out.
心身共に疲れた
Oh, are you down for the count already?
あれ もうグロッキー
Since you came all the way out here
from a big city like Sapporo,
札幌みたいな都会から わざわざ来たんだから
you must've wanted to come
to this school, right?
入りたくて この学校入ったんだろ
Let's tough it out together
till graduation.
卒業まで 一緒に頑張ろうぜ
Nishikawa, Beppu,
what're you guys' goals?
西川と別府は 将来の目標とかあんの
My family has a farm, so I signed up
うち 畑作農家だから
for agricultural sciences
to carry on their business.
継ぐために 農業科に入ったんだもん
Our potatoes are awesome.
うちの芋 うまいぜ
I signed up for food science
because I want to make good food!
俺はいい食いもん作りたいから 食品科に入った
What's with this whole "you're a loser
if you don't have a dream" vibe?
何だ この将来の夢持ってなきゃ 駄目人間みたいな空気は…
Huh? What was that?
何か言った
Nothing.
何でもない
Hey, it's bath time!
あっ 風呂の時間だ 急げ～
Hurry!
Why do we only get fifteen minutes each
to wash up and change clothes?!
着替え入れて １人１５分って おかしいだろが
Is this a prison?
ムショか
Here!
しょうがないだろ 人数多いんだから
What else can they do?
There're too many of us!
Hey, hurry up!
おら 早く出ろ 次の班入るぞ
The next team's waiting!
That's too fast!
早えよ もうちょっと入らせろ
Give us a bit more time!
Shut up!
うるせえ 自由時間が少なくなるだろ
It'll cut into our free time!
Whatever, just wait!
いいから待ってろっつ～の
ちょっ 入ってくんなって！
Hey, don't come in!
I'm really exhausted...
ホント疲れた…
たまには手紙を書いてみようよ
どっかにポストカードでもあったけ
懐かしい顔に見けて
ほんの数行ノスタルジーを
調子はどうですか
忙しくしていますか
無我夢中で探しまわってた
あの夢の具合はどんなだい
気分転換くらいのノリで
一緒に歌わないか
そして無我夢中で探しまわってた
あの夢の続きを語り合おうよ
明日は頑張ろうぜ
今はそこにある未来へ
駆け出して さぁ 行こう
This story is a work of fiction.
The people and groups are fictitious, but the themes relating to food and life are firmly based in reality. Visiting the places and facilities used as models can be dangerous and may result it contracting diseases from the animals. Please enjoy this story as a work of fiction.